talenttrove.com 2008-12-19

# Talent Trove - Privacy Policy

Talent Trove Inc. Privacy Policy Statement  
**Last Updated: March 2nd, 2008**  
Thank you for joining us on Talent Trove, where everyone can be discovered.

TALENTTROVE PRIVACY POLICY  
Talent Trove is an online platform to meet people, make connections and be discovered. This Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect and use the personal information you decide to share, and help you make informed decisions when using Talent Trove  
Talent Trove ("Talent Trove", "us" or "we") respects the privacy of the visitors to its Website, the home page of which is located at http://www.Talent Trove ("Website").  
By using or accessing Talent Trove, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.  
"Personal Information" is information about you that is personally identifiable to you, like your name, address, e-mail address, or phone number, as well as other non-public information that is associated with the foregoing.  
"Anonymous Information" is information that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Information. Anonymous Information does not permit the identification of individual persons. We collect and use Personal Information and Anonymous Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

GENERAL  
We collect Personal Information that you submit to us voluntarily through our Website.  
When you register for the Talent Trove network, we will collect your name, e-mail address, gender, date of birth and ZIP code.  
When you save other Personal Information in your profile we will collect any such information you enter.  
When you enter Personal Information throughout the Talent Trove network using one of the features of the Talent Trove network, for example journals, testimonials, groups, or message boards, we will collect any such information you enter ("Publicly Posted Information").  
When you contact us by sending us an e-mail, we will collect your e-mail addresses and any information contained in the e-mail you send us.  
When you use Talent Trove, you may form relationships, send messages, perform searches, form groups, set up events, respond to job postings and transmit information through various channels. We collect this information so that we can provide you the service and offer personalized features. In most cases, we retain it. Once you register with Talent Trove and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. If you are browsing the Website without registering with Talent Trove, you are anonymous to us, but we will collect the information listed below under Personal Information Collected Via Technology.

USE OF INFORMATION  
Any visitor of the Talent Trove website can view your profile information and photos that you have uploaded to the Talent Trove community. You can control what part of your profile information and photos is visible to visitors of the Talent Trove website and which network of Talent Trove members can see what information.

To provide you with some of the features that the Talent Trove community offers to its members, we may use Personal Information that is stored in your profile after you have requested such features, for example to send invitation e-mails to people that you specified as being interested in joining the Talent Trove community. In order to provide useful information about social networks to people who might be interested in joining the Talent Trove community, we may use your profile information and photos on the Talent Trove website, when we send emails, or when we send general newsletters to members of the Talent Trove community. When you decide to view a member's profile, we may show that Talent Trove member that you chose to view their profile.

If you decide to use certain features of the Talent Trove network (like journals, blogs, groups, message boards and the like), some of the Personal Information you entered into your Talent Trove profile and any information, including Personal Information, that you enter using one of these features, might be used and displayed.

If you choose to use our invitation service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Talent Trove stores this information to send this one-time email, to register a friend connection if your invitation is accepted, and to track the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us to request that we remove this information from our database.

Talent Trove may also collect information about you from other sources, such as newspapers, blogs, instant messaging services, and other users of the Talent Trove service through the operation of the service (e.g., photo tags) in order to provide you with more useful information and a more personalized experience. Talent Trove members can use the search feature to search for other members by different criteria, like location or gender. The Personal Information that Talent Trove members enter into the Talent Trove profile will be used for these searches. Please be aware that any information that is publicly posted throughout the Talent Trove network can be accessed by every visitor of the Website.

Talent Trove may analyze any collected information for its own internal purposes. In addition, Talent Trove may remove personally identifying information from collected information to render it anonymous. Talent Trove may use Anonymous Information for any purpose and disclose Anonymous Information in its discretion.

INFORMATION SHARING & DISCLOSURE  
Talent Trove does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or as otherwise described in this privacy policy.

We provide your Personal Information to third party service providers who work on behalf of or with Talent Trove under confidentiality agreements to provide some of the services and features of the Talent Trove community and to help us communicate with Talent Trove members. These service providers may use your personal information to help Talent Trove communicate with you about offers from Talent Trove and our marketing partners. However, these service providers do not have any independent right to share this information.

If you decide to use one of the additional services that are offered by our partners, such as the e-mail finder service we may forward Personal Information to these partners to enable them to provide the services that you requested.

We also provide information to third-party advertising companies, as described in the next section. Please be aware that the handling of your Personal Information by our partners or the third-party advertising companies is governed by their privacy policy, not ours.

If you would like to know (1) the categories of Personal Information about you that we disclosed in the prior calendar year to third parties for the purposes of the third parties marketing and/or (2) the names and addresses of such third parties, please contact us.

We will disclose information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We may disclose information, if we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected illegal activities or fraud, situations involving the physical safety of any person, violations of Talent Trove's terms of use, or as otherwise required by applicable law. If our company or our assets are acquired by another company, that company will possess the Personal Information collected by us and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements when you visit our Website. These companies may use Personal Information, such as gender or age, and other information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites, such as time of day of the login, IP address or information about the internet service provider (ISP), in order to provide advertisements on the Website about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

PERSONAL INFORMATION CONNECT VIA TECHNOLOGY  
As you navigate the Website, certain information may also be passively collected and stored on our server logs, including your Internet protocol address, browser type, and operating system. We also use Cookies and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URL) to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the solutions and information for which you searched and viewed, or on which of the advertisements displayed on the Website you clicked. This type of information is collected to make our services and solutions more useful to you and to tailor the Talent Trove community experience to meet your special interests and needs.

If you search the Talent Trove community by using a toolbar that Talent Trove, or a third party provides, we may collect Anonymous Information about you automatically, but we will not collect Personal Information.

An "Internet protocol address" or "IP Address" is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. In some cases your IP Address stays the same from browser session to browser session; but if you use a consumer internet access provider, your IP Address probably varies from session to session. We track your IP Address when you login to the Website.

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that a web site sends to your computers hard drive while you are viewing a web site. Talent Trove may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on the Website. Persistent Cookies can be removed by following your Internet browser help file directions. If you choose to disable Cookies, some areas of the Website may not work properly.

Other third parties may place advertisements and cookies on webpages within the Talent Trove network. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one.

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Talent Trove service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the Talent Trove Newsletter, that are considered part of your Talent Trove account. If you would like to opt out of certain messages, log into Talent Trove and go to your account settings by clicking the account link in the top right hand corner. On that page you can edit your preferences. If you would like to delete your account, log into Talent Trove, go to your account settings page by clicking the account link in the top right hand corner. On that page, right below the email address field you will see a link to cancel your account.

CONFIDENTIALITY & SECURITY  
We limit access to personal information about you to employees and third parties who we reasonably believe need access to that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you and your Talent Trove account information is protected by a password that you select. Talent Trove uses industry-standard SSL encryption in certain areas of the Website to protect data transmissions. However, no company, including Talent Trove, can fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information.

OTHER SITES  
Our provision of a link to any other website or location is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such other website or location or its contents. We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for these outside websites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of our Privacy Policy does not apply to these outside websites.

REGARDING CHILDREN  
We do not intentionally gather Personal Information about visitors who are under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information to or on Talent Trove. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible.

CONTACTING US  
Should you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us:

admin@talenttrove.com

Attn: General Counsel

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY  
Talent Trove may update this policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat Personal Information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Talent Trove account or by placing a prominent notice on our Website. If you object to any such changes, you must cease using our Website. Continued use of our Website following notice of any such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.
